Bakke, E. Wight Papers 5522
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Organization and the Individual (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Organization and the Individual (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Organizational Basis of Power (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Organizational Behavior: A Framework of Theory (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Organizational Determinants of Relative Power (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Organizational Factors in Productivity (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Organizational Factors in Productivity (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Organizational Problem Solving (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Organizational Problems in Collective Bargaining (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Organizational Structure and Dynamics (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Origins of the American Revolution Translated into Industrial Relations Language (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Oslo-Yale Leadership Pattern Test, Part I (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Oslo-Yale Leadership Pattern Test, Part II (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Oslo-Yale Leadership Pattern Test, Part III (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Our Faith (Box 9, Folder 21)
- People and Organizations (Box 9, Folder 22)
- People and Organizations (Box 9, Folder 23)
- People and Organizations (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Plans and Progress (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Poetry (Box 9, Folder 26)
- A Positive Labor Market Policy (Box 9, Folder 27)
- A Positive Labor Market Policy (Box 9, Folder 28)
- The Practice and Science of Human Relations (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Premises of a Positive Labor Market (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Pressure of Population on Resources (Box 9, Folder 31)
- The Price of Freedom (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Price of Freedom in Union-Management (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Principles of Adaptive Human Behavior (Later published under the title "Adaptive Human Behavior") (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Principles of Adaptive Human Behavior (Later published under the title "Adaptive Human Behavior") (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Principles of Adaptive Human Behavior (Later published under the title "Adaptive Human Behavior") (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Principles of Human Relations and Training (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Principles that Make and Industrial Organization Work (Box 9, Folder 38)
- The Problem Solving Process (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Processes and Bonds of Organization (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Producers' Exchanges (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Program of Research in Behavior and Relations (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Promoting Labor Peace (Box 10, Folder 5)
- A Prospectus Submitted to the President and Fellows of Yale University (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Protection of Public Interest in Labor-Management Relations (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Public Employees Fair Employment Act, Western New York School Board Institute (Bakke - Speaker) (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Public Image of Labor Unions (Box 10, Folder 9)
- The Public Questions Management and Labor (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Public Understanding of the Role of Industry in the American System (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Quinnipiac College (2 speeches) (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Relief of the Unemployed After Insurance Benefits are Exhausted in Great Britain, Part I (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Relief of the Unemployed After Insurance Benefits are Exhausted in Great Britain, Part II (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Religion of Power (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Report of the Faculty Chairman to the Board of Directors Salzburg Seminar in American Studies (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Research and Practice in Industrial Relations (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Research Methods for Study of Adjustments of Workers to Unemployment (Box 10, Folder 18)
- 1) Research in Industrial Relations, 2) Research Methods for Study of Adjustments of Workers, 3) Research on Economic Folkways (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Retirement Allowances for Non-Professional and Non-Executive Employees of Yale University (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Return to First Principles in Unemployment Compensation (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Revolutionary Democracy, Early Draft (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Revolutionary Democracy, Early Draft (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Revolutionary Democracy, Early Draft (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Revolutionary Democracy, Japan (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Revolutionary Democracy, Japan Book-Notes for Revision (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Revolutionary Democracy, Japan Book-Notes for Revision (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Role of Collective Bargaining in a Competitive Society (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Roots and Soil of Student Activism (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Roots and Soil of Student Activism (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Roots and Soil of Student Activism (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Savitt Sportsmanship Award Banquet (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Scandinavian Speeches, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Sermons (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Social Security (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Social Security (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Social Security in Great Britain (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Social Services for the Unemployed, Parts I and II (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Social Services for the Unemployed, Parts I and II (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Sociological Study of Labor Organizations (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Some Misconceptions About the Why and the What of Unions (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Some Notes on Learning Theory (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Some Sociological Factors in Industrial Relations (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Sources of Conflict Among Functional Groups in Danish Industry (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Speeches, Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Status, Rank and Role (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Status, Rank and Role (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Status, Role and Adjustment Problems of a Nurse in an Industrial Environment (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Strikes and the Public Interest (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Student Activism Inter-University Board (Bakke - Speaker) (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Students on the March: The Cases of Mexico and Columbia (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Students Role in Educational, Social and Economic Development, The Cases of Columbia and Mexico. #1 and #2 Questionnaires (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Students Role in Educational, Social and Economic Development, The Cases of Columbia and Mexico. #1 and #2 Questionnaires (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Supervisory and Management Training in Norway (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Tasks and Acts Incorporated in the Organizational Processes (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Teachers, School Boards and the Employment Relationships (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Teamwork in Industry (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Terms of Organization (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Testimonial Speech for Maurice Davie (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Theoretical Framework of Research in Organizational Behavior (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Unemployment Compensation (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Unemployment in New Haven (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Union Leadership and the Public Interest (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Unions, Management and the Public (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Unions, Management and the Public, Chapters 4 and 5 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Unions, Management and the Public, Some chapters and notes on unions and management (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Unions, Management and the Public, First drafts finished) (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Unions, Management and the Public, First drafts finished) (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Unions, Management and the Public, Industrial Relations System (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Unions, Management and the Public, Bakke and Kerr, Second Carbon (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Unions, Management and the Public, II. Development of Unionism (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Unions, Management and the Public, III. Material used for research (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Unions, Management and the Public, IV. Development of Union Leadership and Administration (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Unions, Management and the Public, IV. Development of Unions Membership and Dem. (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Unions, Management and the Public, V. Management and the Unions (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Unions, Management and the Public, V. Management and the Unions (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Unions, Management and the Public, V. Management and the Unions (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Unions, Management and the Public, VI. Industrial Conflict (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Unions, Management and the Public, VII. Collective Bargaining (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Unions, Management and the Public, VIII. Politics and Industrial Relations (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Unions, Management and the Public, IX. Patterns of Relationship (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Unions, Management and the Public, IX. Patterns of Relationship (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Unions, Management and the Public, X. General Employment and Hours Security for Workers (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Unions, Management and the Public, X. General Employment and Hours Security for Workers (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XI. Wage Determination (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XII, Wages and the Economy (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XII, Wages and the Economy (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XII, Wages and the Economy (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XII, Wages and the Economy (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XIII. Industrial Relations and the Wider Community Law and Monopoly (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XIII. Industrial Relations and the Wider Community Law and Monopoly (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XIII. Industrial Relations and the Wider Community Law and Monopoly (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XIII. Industrial Relations and the Wider Community, Religion and Ethics (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XIII. Industrial Relations and the Wider Community, Religion and Ethics (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XIII. Industrial Relations and the Wider Community, Religion and Ethics (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Unions, Management and the Public, Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Unions, Management and the Public, Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XIV. Toward Tomorrow (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Unions, Management and the Public, XIV. Toward Tomorrow (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Universities and Training (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Unveiling the Tator Portraits (Box 13, Folder 12)
- The Way of the Cross (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Welcome from Trustees of Quinnipiac College and What is Ahead in Industrial Relations (Box 13, Folder 14)
- What is Wrong with Unemployment Compensation (Box 13, Folder 15)
- What Management Expects of Unions and What the Unions Expect of Management (Box 13, Folder 16)
- What Value has Basic Research in Human Relations (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Why Work (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Why Join a Union (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Why Workers Join Unions (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Work of the Yale Labor and Management Center (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Workers, Management and Unions (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Workers Wanted (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Workers Wanted (Box 13, Folder 24)
- 1) Yale Interprets the News, 2) Yale Labor and Management Center, 3) Yale Technology Project. (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Accidents to Employees at Labor and Management Centers (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Address List and American Arbitration Association Newsletter (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Advanced Management - Office Executive (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Anrod, Charles (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Argyris, Chris (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Argyris Article (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Bargaining on Productivity (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Bargaining Over General Wage Changes by Lloyd Reynolds (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Bibliographies (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Business Decision-Making (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Collective Bargaining and the Concept of Contract by Neil Chamberlain (Box 14, Folder 11)
- College of Continuing Education (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Concept of Mores (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Cornell University, New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Course in Organizational Theory and E) Definitions and Dimensions and F) Tests of Organization (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Course in Organizational Theory, G) Terms (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Course in Organizational Theory, H) Hypotheses and J) Managerial Assumptions and Premises (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Criticism of the Marginal Productivity Approach by Neil Chamberlain (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Ely Culbertson's Peace Plan (Box 14, Folder 19)
- The Development of Federal Relief Program, 1936 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  December
- Early Ideas for Research (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Employers Culture and Community Standards (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Employers' Hiring Policies (Box 14, Folder 23)
- European Productivity Agency, see: Foreign Operations Administration (Box 14, Folder 24)
- European Productivity Agency (EPA), see: Foreign Operations Administration (FOA) correspondence (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Faith and Mental Health, see: Crane Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 26)
- First Four Years, see: Seymore and Carnegie Corp. Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Foreign Operation Administration (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Foundation for Research on Human Behavior, Annual Reports and Newsletters (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Fourth Report to Dr. E. W. Bakke from Chris Argyris (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Fragments (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Functional Roles of Union and Management, by Neil Chamberlain (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Furrier Strike, Mr. George Lewis (Box 14, Folder 33)
- General Theory of the Organization and Management, see Dan Duncan Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Gorden, Paul J. (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Grant, Fulbright-Denmark (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Gross, B. (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Gross, B. (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Hilton BBC (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Hobart College (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Human Relations in an Expanding Company and Job Horizons, Reviews and Comments (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Ideas (Box 14, Folder 42)
- International Industrial Relations Association, First World Congress, Part I (Box 14, Folder 43)
- International Industrial Relations Association, First World Congress, Part II (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Introduction to Field Theory and Interactpersonality Fundamentals for Administrators (Box 14, Folder 45)
- The Irregular Economy: Informal Work Patterns in the Urban Ghetto (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Japan, The Occupational Revolution: The Adaptation of the People of Japan to a New Day, by E.W.B., Late Fall, - Mailing List and Judas, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Job Applicants (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Job Applicants (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Laboratory for Labor Problems at Yale (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Man and Automation: Report of the Proceedings of a Conference Sponsored by the Society for Applied Anthropology (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Management Directive Function and Management Representative Function (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Management in Motion by Neil Chamberlain (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Manuscript Preparation (Box 15, Folder 4)
- The Mapping of Wage Radiation (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Reviews and Comments (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Morse Chain Company Study by E. William Noland (Box 15, Folder 7)
- National Council of the Churches of Christ in the United States of America. Information Service (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Navy Department (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Navy Department (Box 15, Folder 10)
- New Furniture, 24 Hillhouse Avenue (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Notes on Interaction (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Nyman's Outlines (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Organized Labor and Management Control (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Over-Education (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Patterns of Leadership... and Pegler, Westbrook (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Position Description Questionnaire (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Power of Attorney and Prospect Hill School (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Project of Research, Training and Publications Related to Organizational Behavior (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Publicity (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Quinnipiac College (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Quinnipiac College (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Radical Movement (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Research Method, I.H.R. (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Schedules, Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Slichter, Sumner (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Slichter, Sumner (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Slichter, Sumner (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Slichter, Sumner (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Slichter, Sumner (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Social Science Reporter (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Social Security (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Society in the Making by Karl Bakke (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Some Preliminary Thoughts on Organizational Theory by Chris Argyris (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Some Thoughts on Collective Bargaining Systems... (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Steeltown, Reviews and Comments (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Structure of Labor Markets, Reviews and Comments (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Tomorrow's Counselor and Toward a Social Science (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Toward a Science of Human Behavior (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Toward a Theory and Practice of Social Architecture (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Training Directors Contact List (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Unemployment Insurance (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Union Challenge to Management Control, Reviews and Comments (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Union Organizing Songs and University Council (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Upjohn Institute, Project on Manpower (Box 15, Folder 45)
- "Vinduct" (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Ware, Norman, Haverhill Experiment (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Webb, Sidney and Who Controls Union Policy by Joseph Shister (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Whyte, William Foote (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Workers' Language (Box 16, Folder 4)
- The Worker's View of Job Opportunity, by Lloyd Reynolds and Joseph Shister (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Telephone Company and Union Analysis and Explanation of Study (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Analysis Functional Specification, Accounting Department (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Analysis of Suggestion System Inadequacies for Plant Headquarter Employees (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Analysis of Suggestion System Inadequacies - Employees (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Analysis of Suggestion System Inadequacies - Management (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Analysis of Suggestion System Inadequacies - Management, written copies (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Communications System Instructions Employees, Management, Union Off. (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers, Inc., Constitution and By-Laws (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Contract between the SNETCO and Connecticut Union of Telephone (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, N.W.C. (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Division and District - Mgt. Plant, Traffic, Commercial (Box 16, Folder 16)
- District and Division Management, Commercial Department, Management Analysis (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Employee Interview Form (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Employee Interviews (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Employee Interviews (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Exhibits 1 - 15 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Exhibits 16 - 21 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- General Observations, Commercial (Box 16, Folder 23)
- General Observations, Headquarters (Box 16, Folder 24)
- General Observations, Plant (Box 16, Folder 25)
- General Observations, Traffic (Box 16, Folder 26)
- General Observations, Traffic (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Guides for Analysis of Functional Specifications, Employees, Management, Union Officers (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Human Relations, Book 1 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Human Relations in Management (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Human Relations in Management, Book 2 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Information Concerning the SNETCO (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Information Concerning the SNETCO (Box 17, Folder 2)
- "Interim Function Specs." (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Interview Schedule, Job Specification (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Interviews: Group IV: Torrington, Norwich, Danbury, New Britain, Waterbury, Stamford, Hartford, New Haven (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Interviews, R and P (Box 17, Folder 6)
- KRA's Commercial Department Management Analysis, Commercial Headquarters (Box 17, Folder 7)
- KRA's Status System, Executive Department Employees (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Pat Larrow's Notes and Summaries (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Local Plant Management (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Method, Basic Tables, First Analysis Summary-Functional Spec. (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous old material that probably belong somewhere among exhibits (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous materials on union officers which was never used (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous materials on union officers which was never used (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Notes, Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Notes of Interviews (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Operating Codes (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Organization Charts Outline of the Duties of the Plant Deputy Field Personnel (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Plant Department, General Functions (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Poole, Observations (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Questionnaires (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Questionnaires (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Reward and Penalty System, Chapter in Bonds of Organization (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Richardson's Material (Box 17, Folder 24)
- SNETCO, Accounting Department (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Test of Efficiency for Bonds of Organization (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Telephone Company Study, Dictating and Typing Code Words, Union and Management (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Traffic Headquarter Employees (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Training and Organizational Material Accounting (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Union Charters (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Union Officers, Interviews (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Working with Operators (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Yale Labor and Management Center Telephone Company Study (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Af - Accounting, Employees (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Af - Definition Commercial, 4 Exchange Employees (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Af - Definition Employees Commercial, Hartford and New Haven (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Af - Definition Employees Commercial, Waterbury and Stamford (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Af - Definition Employees Commercial, New Britain and Danbury (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Af - Definition Employees Commercial, Torrington and Norwich (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Af - Definition General Engineering and Executive, New Haven (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Af - Definition Plant, Traffic, Commercial Headquarters, Employees (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Af - Definition Employees, Inside Plant, Group B (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Af - Definition Employees, Inside Plant, Hartford and New Haven (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Af - Definition Employees, Inside Plant, Waterbury and Stamford (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Af - Definition Employees, Inside Plant, Danbury and New Britain (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Af - Definition Employees, Inside and Outside, Norwich (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Af - Definition Employees, Outside Plant, Group B (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Af - Definition Employees, Inside and Outside, Hartford and New Haven (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Af - Definition Employees, Outside Plant, Stamford (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Af - Definition Employees, Outside Plant, Waterbury (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Af - Definition Employees, Outside Plant, New Britain (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Af - Definition Employees, Inside and Outside, Hartford and Danbury (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Af - Definition Employees Traffic, Group 4 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Af - Definition Employees Traffic, Group 4 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, Group 5 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, Hartford (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, New Haven (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, Waterbury (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, Stamford (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, New Britain (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, Danbury (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, Torrington (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, Norwich (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Af - Definition Employees, Traffic, Inside and Outside Plant (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Accounting-New Haven (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Commercial Dist and Division (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Plant Dist and Division (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Traffic Dist and Division (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Executive (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Commercial Field (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Plant Field (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Af - Definition Employees, Management, Traffic Field (Box 18, Folder 39)